Stop!
不要
Please stop!
快停手
I'll say it. I said, I'll say it!
我會說 我說的
Don't make me!
放過我吧
Please suck...
請吸…
No, I just can't do this!
不要 我做不到
Don't make me!
放過我吧
Stop!
不要
Help me!
救救我
Please stop!
快停手
Stop!
停手
Wait!
不要
I'll say it.
我會說的
Suck on my nipples.
請吸我的乳頭
Suck them!
請吸
The school princess.
學校的公主
You've heard it before, Miyuki.
你之前聽說過嗎
All the guys refer to Kotomi as the princess.
所有的男生都說琴未是公主
Did you see her wearing that ugly granny underwear?
你看到她穿媽媽的內衣嗎
Well, I've worn granny panties on occasion.
嗯我有時也會穿媽媽的內衣
If you want to gossip...
如果你太無聊的話…
you can do that with somebody else, Rika.
你可以找其他人啊 理香
But I know you feel the same way I do about her, Miyuki.
但我知道你和我對他同樣有感覺美由紀
I know what you mean.
我知道你你想什麼的
Sometimes, I wear bloomers over my panties.
有時候我也會穿的比較短
You're assuming incorrectly.
你想太多了吧
Don't worry.
沒關係啊
It's not like I'll tell anyone.
我不會告訴任何人的
You two are looking awfully cozy over there.
你們兩個在哪里說什麼秘密啊
You can mind your own business.
你別多管閒事
Was I right?
我說對了嗎
Of course not.
當然不是
No!
哈
Stop!
不要
Hey, stop looking at me!
嘿不要看我
Don't look!
不要看我
Close the window, damn it!
快把窗關上
No!
不要
A princess?
是公主嗎
No!
不行
Wait!
不要
Get away from me!
不要這樣 不要
Please, let me go!
不要這樣
She's no longer a princess anymore.
她不再是公主了
Help me!
求求你
He won't kill us if we both...
他不會殺我們只要我們都…
masturbate.
在他面前手淫
Will you please do it?
請你照做吧
I can't...
什麼…
I can't do that!
我不能這樣做
I can't, please, I've never done it before!
求求你 我之前沒有做過
I don't know how, either!
我也不知道該怎麼做
But you have an idea?
但是你有其他辦法嗎
If you show me how...
我們到底該這樣做…
I'll do it along with you.
我會按你的方法做的
Isaku Respect Episode 2
遺作 ～Respect～
Scent of a bitch:
第二幕 母豬的香味
Miyuki Sakaki
Part A 榊 美由紀
You want me to?
你想要我
Don't, I said I'll do it.
不要我會照做的
What did I do to you!
我沒對你做過什麼
Why should I?
為什麼你要這樣
These are bloomers, not my underwear!
這是運動短褲 不是我的內衣
I'm going to throw him in jail later!
我以後也不會在穿了
Feels good, this feels really good!
很舒服 這感覺好舒服
Can't hold it!
不可能
Don't look!
不要看
No!
不要
That's gross!
你這混蛋
Never!
不可以
I would rather die, than allow this creep...
寧願死也不可讓這這混蛋…
to see me like this!
見到這樣子的我
What are you doing?
您在做什麼
Don't listen to him like a slave.
不要想奴隸的聽從他
You have no right to talk.
你沒有說話的權利
You were forced to piss in front of us...
你也不是在我們面前小便嗎…
and you seemed to enjoy it.
你似乎很喜歡這樣做
Don't!
不要
I want to forget about that.
你要把這忘記掉
Please don't remind me!
不要再提起了
Become a slave!
成為一個奴隸吧
Slave?
奴隸
If you become a slave...
只要你成為一個奴隸…
you can forget about everything.
你就可以忘掉這一切
Didn't masturbating feel good for you, too?
手淫的感覺很好吧
Just be honest with yourself.
你還是老實點吧
Come with me.
跟我來吧
It's your turn now.
現在該輪到你了
I think...
我想…
I'm prepared to do this.
我已經準備好了
I would like to get to it...
我想做…
right away, but...
馬上就做…
Hey!
喂喂
Have...
有見到…
you seen my panties around here?
有見到我的運動褲嗎
Darn, It was one of my favorites!
嗯 那是我最喜歡的
Rika, I need your swimsuit!
理香快點脫下來吧
Miyuki needs to use it.
美由紀需要穿它
I'll take it off.
我知道了
Yes!
不要
Give me more, please, Isaku!
請給我更多 遺作
Here, but I think it might be a bit small!
好了 不過我覺得會小了點
That's for me?
這個
That's the rule.
這是規則
You're soaking wet.
你已經濕了
You smell down there, too.
讓我也嘗一下吧
Yes, more!
繼續
I want it harder!
繼續 我想要更多
Come on!
來了
Faster!
快點
Yeah, harder, too!
繼續 給我更多
No!
不要
That was a...
這裡是
dream?
夢
Help me!
救救我
Are you okay, Miyuki?
美由紀 你沒事吧
No, stop it!
不要快停手
That voice...
這個聲音…
I don't know anything.
我也不知道
I can't take it!
我不要這樣
That hurts!
好疼
We have to go help Kotomi!
我們必須想辦法就琴未
I'm sorry, Miyuki!
對不起美由紀
What are you doing?
您在做什麼
I'm sorry.
對不起
No, stop!
不住手
I don't have a choice.
我沒有得選擇
I'm sorry!
對不起
No!
不要
Stop it!
等等
No!
不可以
Damn it!
怎麼了
Hold on!
不要啊
No!
不要
I guess it's my turn now?
現在應該可以了
I have to let you watch.
請你好好看吧
Go on.
繼續看下去
Kenta?
健太
Kenta, can you hear me!
健太你能聽到嗎
Isaku's hurting us!
你在那…
I can't!
不要這樣
I can't, like this!
我不想這樣
I can't talk like this.
我不能這樣子繼續講下去
I'll say it, so stop!
我會繼續說的
Hey, Kenta.
健太
Kotomi has pale, smooth skin.
琴未有著嫩白光滑的皮膚
Please, I'm begging you!
求求不 不要這樣
Don't smell that!
不要聞那裡
Her skin smells very sweet and sticky.
她的皮膚聞起來好香
Just like with Rika and Akemi...
就像理香和明美一樣…
I should spread her legs wide open, and stuff her...
我要把他們的腿完全分開並且用我的東西填滿它…
pussy with my hard cock.
我會讓他們十分舒服的
Don't!
我…
No!
不要
I can't believe that filthy bastard...
我不能相信我竟然被這畜生…
raped me!
強姦了
Please, no more!
求求你 求求你
Let me go!
不要
I'm sorry, I wish there was something I could do!
對不起 我想我能做到的
But...
的但…
I can't!
不可以這樣
I can't hold it anymore!
我不能這樣做
No!
不要
I don't want to go through that ever again.
我不想再次這樣
Stop!
不要啊
It's coming out!
要出來了
No more enemas!
不想在被灌腸了
I'm really sorry.
我真的很抱歉
That's right!
所以
Kotomi Asakawa
Part B 淺川 琴未
About the princess' prized pussy...
公主的珍貴的私處…
you know you've been dreaming night and day...
你時時刻刻想著的東西
about fucking it.
想得到的東西
It's so plump and juicy.
是如此肥美和多汁
That hurts!
好疼
Ready, Kotomi!
準備好了嗎琴未
Sure.
好了
Don't move so much, Kotomi!
不要亂動琴未
Hold on!
但是
I'm surprised that she has a large, well-developed clitoris.
我很驚訝她擁有一個發達的陰蒂
No, stop!
不要 不要 不要
If you flick it around with your tongue...
如果你用舌頭輕輕觸碰它…
she'll start to moan.
她就會開始呻吟了
Her pussy will get juicier.
直到高潮
No!
不要
It reeks, unfortunately.
不幸的是 那已經開始發臭了
It doesn't reek.
不是的
Just because she's pretty...
雖然他她很漂亮…
doesn't mean her pussy's not going to reek like garbage.
但這並不代表她的私處不會像垃圾一樣發臭
She had to piss a while back...
她不得不儘快小便…
so it smells like piss.
所以他的小便一樣發臭了
It's so bad, I have to hold my breath.
既然如此糟糕我必須屏氣呼吸
You saw Akemi's video already, right?
你已經看到明美視頻了吧
No!
不要
Don't make me!
放過我吧
I'll do it!
我會做的
I made them piss out everything in their bladder.
我會把他們髒的東西全部給拍打出來
I know you're a dirty pervert.
的我知道你是喜歡肮髒的人
I'm sure you watched it all!
我相信你能看到這一切
Even the bonus shots!
就像射籃一樣
You liked it, right?
你很喜歡對吧
I know all the little boys at school are fascinated with this.
我知道學校所有的男生都會被迷住的
You all talk about the golden shower, right?
你們都很在意那黃色的液體對吧
No, stop it!
不不要
You wouldn't expect it from her...
你從來不會注意他那裡
but she has really big tits.
但是他確實有一堆很大的奶子
You noticed it at the pool.
你在泳池一見識過
She's got a killer ass, too.
她那豐滿的屁股和那突出乳頭吧
They're big, so you can see their shape, right through her swimsuit.
它們是在太突出 所以你隔著泳衣也能看到吧
Just...
那是
Stop!
不要
They liked being pinched.
她喜歡被捏
It feels good.
很有感覺哦
Don't be gentle, they want you to be rough with them.
不要溫柔 她想要粗暴點的
That hurts, you're hurting my nipples!
不是的 你不要亂說
You see?
是嗎
Either way, even if she was ugly...
隨便選種方式蹂躪她吧
her blow jobs would make up for it.
她會自動配合你的
There's no doubt, she can be crowned the blow job queen.
毫無疑問她是一個淫蕩的女生
That's enough preview for right now.
好了 預覽到這裡了
Let's get started with the fucking.
讓我們儘快開始吧
Kenta!
健太
Did you want to see the princess in her underwear?
你希望能見到公主的內衣嗎
Did you want to feel her soft tits in your hand?
想把它的雙乳捏再手上嗎
Stop!
不要啊
Hear her scream when she comes?
想聽到她的呻吟聲碼
No!
不要
Watch her pussy quiver and pucker?
想觀賞她那顫抖的下陰嗎
No, stop, I want to die!
不要 不要會死的
Everything you wanted to feel, I'll do it and tell you about it.
你想要的一切 我都可以做和告訴你的
No!
不要
Too bad you can't smell her stinky pussy!
可惜你聞不到她那發臭的下陰
Enjoy the sound of her getting fucked.
只能欣賞她那淫蕩的呻吟聲了
Stop!
求求你
I'd rather die than lose my virginity to you!
我寧願死也不想把處女給你
Just kill me!
殺了我吧
The first time?
第一次
Was it painful?
真的很疼嗎
Rika, that's really rude!
理香不要這麼大聲
But Kotomi, aren't you curious, too?
但是 琴未 難道你不好奇嗎
I'm not.
我…
I don't mind at all.
就是啊 琴未
After all...
最終…
I think I'm the only one that has any experience here.
再這裡還是只有我一個有這經驗
That's not something you should be bragging about.
你不是在自誇吧
You can't be a real woman unless you've experienced it.
你沒經歷過吧 小妹妹
How does it feel?
感覺好嗎
Very good.
當然好
It feels good.
真的很好嘛
I'm going to have to find my prince!
我必須儘快找到自己的王子
A prince?
王子
The first guy should...
第一次…
be with someone dreamy, right?
是要和自己喜歡的人做 不是嗎
I agree.
是啊
I think we all fantasize about this.
我想這是我們大家的夢想吧
Yes, I can handle it.
嗯 我想我沒問題的
It's okay!
繼續吧
No!
不要
Pull it out!
拔出來
That hurts!
好疼
No, you're really hurting me!
好疼… 誰來… 誰來…
Please!
誰來…
Somebody help me.
誰來救救我
Mommy!
媽媽
Help me, mommy!
求我媽媽
No!
不要
Help me!
救救我
No more!
好人
Just stop!
快停啊
I can't...
不行了…
take anymore!
好疼
Hey Rika?
理香
I won't get you involved, but...
我不需要你參與 但是
I need you to help me.
我需要你的幫忙
Let me die!
不行了
Not inside!
不要在裡面
Don't come inside!
絕對不可以
Excuse me!
遺作
Rika had to...
理香 她…
go to the bathroom really badly.
去洗手間是在太久了
So...
所以…
don't worry about me.
你不用擔心我
I don't want to fight you anymore.
我已經放棄反抗了
After all, I'm...
畢竟我是…
your slave, right?
您的奴隸